Guide to the Seattle Department of Parks and Recreation Planning, Construction and Maintenance Records 1928-1994
Seattle Municipal Archives
- Project files, 1928-1994
  - Jackson Park Golf Course, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 29/27)
  - Jackson Park Golf Course Restrooms, 1968 (Box-folder 29/28)
  - Jefferson Park Golf Course Irrigation System, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 29/29)
  - Jackson Park Maintenance Facility, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 29/30)
  - Jefferson Park Lawn Bowling, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 29/31)
  - Kobe Terrace / Yesler Terrace Mini Park, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 30/1)
  - Kobe Terrace / Yesler Terrace Mini Park Correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder 30/2)
  - Kobe Terrace / Yesler Terrace Mini Park, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 30/3)
  - Kobe Terrace / Yesler Terrace Mini Park, 1975 (Box-folder 30/4)
  - Kobe Terrace / Yesler Terrace Mini Park, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 30/5)
  - Kobe Terrace / Yesler Terrace Mini Park Contracts Drawings, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 30/6)
  - Kobe Terrace / Yesler Terrace Mini Park Newspaper Clippings, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 30/7)
  - Jefferson Park Recreation Center, 1966-1976 (Box-folder 30/8)
  - Kerry Park, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 30/9)
  - Kubota Gardens, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 30/10)
  - Lake City Community Center Playground, 1963-1971 (Box-folder 30/11)
  - Lake City Community Center, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 30/12)
  - Lake City Community Center Contracts Drawings, 1975 (Box-folder 30/13)
  - Lake City Community Center Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box-folder 30/14)
  - Lake City Mini Park Contracts, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 30/15)
  - Lake City Mini Park, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 30/16)
  - Lake City Mini Park, 1980 (Box-folder 30/17)
  - Lake City Mini Park (Incl. Drawings), 1981 (Box-folder 30/18)
  - Lake City Park, 1981 (Box-folder 30/19)
  - Lake City Park (Incl. Photographs), 1982 (Box-folder 30/20)
  - Lake City Mini Park Newspaper Clippings, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 30/21)
  - Lake City Treatment Plant ( includes Thornton, Creek environs, aerial photographs ), 1969-1981 (Box-folder 30/22)
  - Lake Union Asphalt Plant, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 30/23)
  - Lake Washington Blvd. - Seward Park - Bicycle Path, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 30/24)
  - Lake Washington Rowing Club Agreement, 1973-1981 (Box-folder 30/25)
  - Lake Washington Seawall Improvements, 1975 (Box-folder 30/26)
  - Lakewood Playground, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 30/27)
  - Lakewood Moorage, 1968 (Box-folder 30/28)
  - Langston Hughes Community Center Passageway, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 30/29)
  - Laurelhurst Playfield Children's Play Area, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 30/30)
  - Laurelhurst Tennis Court Lighting, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 30/31)
  - Laurelhurst Tennis Court Lighting, 1977 (Box-folder 30/32)
  - Laurelhurst Playfield Practice Tennis Courts, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 30/33)
  - Leschi Moorage Renovation, 1982 (Box-folder 31/1)
  - Leschi Moorage Renovation, 1983 (Box-folder 31/2)
  - Leschi Moorage Renovation, 1984 (Box-folder 31/3)
  - Leschi Moorage Improvements, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 31/4)
  - Leschi - Concessionaire Development, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 31/5)
  - Leschi Playground, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 31/6)
  - Leschi Playground, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 31/7)
  - Leschi / Madrona Bulkhead, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 31/8)
  - Licton Springs Contract Drawings, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 31/9)
  - Licton Springs Park, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 31/10)
  - Licton Springs Park, 1973 (Box-folder 31/11)
  - Licton Springs Park, 1974 (Box-folder 31/12)
  - Licton Springs, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 31/13)
  - Licton Springs Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box-folder 31/14)
  - Lincoln Park Colman Pool Contract, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 31/15)
  - Lincoln Park Colman Pool, 1968-1977 (Box-folder 31/16)
  - Lincoln Park Restroom, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 31/17)
  - Lincoln Park Program Planning, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 31/18)
  - Lincoln Park Improvements, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 31/19)
  - Lincoln Park Improvements Contract, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 31/20)
  - Lincoln Park Newspaper Clippings, 1974 (Box-folder 31/21)
  - Lincoln Park Seawall Renovation Beach Restoration, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 31/22)
  - Lincoln Park Seawall Renovation Beach Restoration, 1983 (Box-folder 31/23)
  - Lincoln Park Seawall Renovation Beach Restoration, 1984 (Box-folder 31/24)
  - Lincoln Park U.S. Army Beach Study, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 31/25)
  - Lincoln Park Maintenance Contracts Facility, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 31/26)
  - Lincoln Park Maintenance Facility, 1982 (Box-folder 31/27)
  - Lincoln Park Maintenance Facility, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 31/28)
  - Lowman Beach - Metro Combined Sewer Overflow Holding Tank Reports Drawings, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 32/1)
  - Lowman Beach Photographs, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 32/2)
  - Lowman Beach Combined Sewer Overflow Project, 1979 (Box-folder 32/3)
  - Lowman Beach Metro Combined Sewer Overflow Project, 1981 (Box-folder 32/4)
  - Lowman Beach Park Metro CSO Project, 1982 (Box-folder 32/5)
  - Lowman Beach Metro Pump Station, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 32/6)
  - Loyal Heights Playfield, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 32/7)
  - Loyal Heights Grounds Improvements Contracts, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 32/8)
  - Loyal Heights Grounds Maintenance, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 32/9)
  - Loyal Heights Grounds Maintenance, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 32/10)
  - Lower Woodland Tennis Court Lighting, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 32/11)
  - Madison Park Bathhouse, 1984 (Box-folder 32/12)
  - Madison Park Bathhouse Renovation Contracts, 1984 (Box-folder 32/13)
  - Madison Park Bathhouse Renovation, 1983 (Box-folder 32/14)
  - Madison Park Play Area, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 32/15)
  - Madison Park Tennis Court Lighting, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 32/16)
  - Madrona Briar Patch Park, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 32/17)
  - Madrona Bathhouse Dance Theater (Incl. Drawings), 1970-1971 (Box-folder 32/18)
  - Madrona Bathhouse Rehabilitation, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 32/19)
  - Madrona Playground Lighting, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 32/20)
  - Madrona Playground 34th East Pike Street Park, 1978 (Box-folder 32/21)
  - Madrona Playground Phase II, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 32/22)
  - Magnolia Community Center Improvements, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 32/23)
  - Magnolia Community Center (Incl. Photographs), 1977-1978 (Box-folder 32/24)
  - Magnolia Community Center Improvements, 1979 (Box-folder 32/25)
  - Magnolia Community Center Design Contract, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 32/26)
  - Magnolia Community Center Improvements Construction Meeting Reports, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 32/27)
  - Magnolia Community Center Groundbreaking / Dedication, 1980 (Box-folder 32/28)
  - Magnolia Community Center Parking Variance, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 32/29)
  - Magnolia Community Club Improvements, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 32/30)
  - Magnolia Community Center Parking Lot Lighting, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 32/31)
  - Magnolia Playfield Lighting Ord. 100782, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 33/1)
  - Magnolia Playfield Lighting, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 33/2)
  - Magnolia Playfield Tennis Courts, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 33/3)
  - Magnolia Tide Lands, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 33/4)
  - Magnolia Tide Lands, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 33/5)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point - Airplanes, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 33/6)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Airplanes, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 33/7)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point - Disposition, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 33/8)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Goals Objectives, 1976 (Box-folder 33/9)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Graphics Maps, 1976 (Box-folder 33/10)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Owls, 1979 (Box-folder 33/11)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Block Grant Funding, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 33/12)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Bureau of Outdoor Recreation, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 33/13)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point: Funding / Appropriations, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 33/14)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Community Citizen Group, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 33/15)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point - Sand Point Citizen's Committee, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 33/16)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point - Sand Point Community Liaison Committee Minutes, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 33/17)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point - Sand Point Community Liaison Committee Minutes, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 33/18)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point: Sand Point Liaison Committee Correspondence Notes, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 33/19)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point - Suggested Uses, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 33/20)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point - suggested uses, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 33/21)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point - Performing Arts Center proposal, 1974 (Box-folder 33/22)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Proposed Sailing Program, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 33/23)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Community Group presentations, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 33/24)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Review Comments, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 33/25)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Construction Reports, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 33/26)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Reports Studies, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 33/27)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Access, 1972 (Box-folder 33/28)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Access, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 33/29)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Easements( includes easements ), 1977-1979 (Box-folder 34/1)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Easement Documents Access, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 34/2)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Design Contract, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 34/3)
  - Magnuson - Deed Legal Description, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 34/4)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point, U of Washington, 1976 (Box-folder 34/5)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Water System, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 34/6)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Washington State Aeronautics Commission (includes lawsuit), 1975 (Box-folder 34/7)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point General Services Administration, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 34/8)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point US Army Corps of Engineers Permits, 1979 (Box-folder 34/9)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Shoreline Permit, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 34/10)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point - US Navy Easements Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 34/11)
  - Magnuson - Dedication, 1977 (Box-folder 34/12)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Correspondence, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 34/13)
  - Magnuson - Correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder 34/14)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Correspondence, 1974 (Box-folder 34/15)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point - Correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 34/16)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point - Correspondence, 1976 (Box-folder 34/17)
  - Sand Point - Magnuson Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 34/18)
  - Magnuson Project File, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 34/19)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point - Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 34/20)
  - Magnuson Newspaper Clippings, 1974 (Box-folder 34/21)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Newspaper Clippings, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 34/22)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point - Trees, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 35/1)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Design Concept Plan, 1975 (Box-folder 35/2)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point - Environmental Impact Statement, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 35/3)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point EI's, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 35/4)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), 1974-1975 (Box-folder 35/5)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), 1976-1977 (Box-folder 35/6)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), 1977-1979 (Box-folder 35/7)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Improvements, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 35/8)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Improvements, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 35/9)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Improvements, 1981 (Box-folder 35/10)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Drawings, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 35/11)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Improvements, 1982 (Box-folder 35/12)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Improvements, 1982 (Box-folder 35/13)
  - Magnuson / Sand Point Improvements, 1983 (Box-folder 35/14)
  - Major Urban Parks - Automatic Irrigation, 1976 (Box-folder 35/15)
  - Major Urban Parks - Automatic Irrigation Systems, 1977 (Box-folder 35/16)
  - Major Urban Parks - Automatic Irrigation, 1978 (Box-folder 35/17)
  - Major Parks Automatic Irrigation ( includes Green Lake deposition ), 1979-1983 (Box-folder 35/18)
  - Maplewood / Beacon Hill Acquisition, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 36/1)
  - Maplewood / Beacon Hill Playfield Design Services Contract, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 36/2)
  - Maplewood / Beacon Hill Playfield Community Input, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 36/3)
  - Maplewood / Beacon Hill Playfield, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 36/4)
  - Maplewood / Beacon Hill Playfield - Drawings Maps, 1973 (Box-folder 36/5)
  - Maplewood / Beacon Hill Playfield, 1973 (Box-folder 36/6)
  - Maplewood / Beacon Hill Playfield, 1974 (Box-folder 36/7)
  - Maplewood / Beacon Hill Playfield, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 36/8)
  - Martha Washington Site Study - Background, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 36/9)
  - Martha Washington Site Study - John Morse Association, 1979 (Box-folder 36/10)
  - Martha Washington Site Study - Background, 1979 (Box-folder 36/11)
  - Martha Washington Site Study - Background, 1979 (Box-folder 36/12)
  - Martha Washington Site Study - Background, 1980 (Box-folder 36/13)
  - Martha Washington Site Study, 1981 (Box-folder 36/14)
  - Martha Washington Site Study, 1982 (Box-folder 36/15)
  - Martha Washington Site Study, 1983 (Box-folder 36/16)
  - Matthews Beach, 1928-1950 (Box-folder 36/17)
  - Matthews Beach, 1950-1959 (Box-folder 36/18)
  - Matthews Beach, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 36/19)
  - Matthews Beach Land Acquisition, 1953-1967 (Box-folder 36/20)
  - Matthews Beach, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 36/21)
  - Matthews Beach Maps Drawings, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 36/22)
  - Matthews Beach - Project Description and Planning, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 36/23)
  - Matthews Beach Contracts, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 36/24)
  - Matthews Beach Acquisition, 1970 (Box-folder 36/25)
  - Matthews Beach Funding, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 36/26)
  - Matthews Beach, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 36/27)
  - Matthews Beach, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 36/28)
  - Matthews Beach, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 36/29)
  - Matrix Management Group Management Consultant Services, 1981 (Box-folder 37/1)
  - Matrix Management Group - Consultant Services, 1982 (Box-folder 37/2)
  - Meadowbrook Playfield Shelterhouse, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 37/3)
  - Meadowbrook Swimming Pool Planning Program, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 37/4)
  - Meadowbrook / Nathan Hale Swimming Pool, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 37/5)
  - Meadowbrook / Nathan Hale Swimming Pool, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 37/6)
  - Meadowbrook / Nathan Hale Pool, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 37/7)
  - Meadowbrook Swimming Pool Newspaper Clippings, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 37/8)
  - Me - Kwa - Mooks Park (Schmitz Waterfront Park), 1968-1975 (Box-folder 37/9)
  - Me - Kwa - Mooks Park, 1976 (Box-folder 37/10)
  - Me - Kwa - Mooks Park, 1977 (Box-folder 37/11)
  - Me - Kwa - Mooks Park ( Schmitz Waterfront Park ), 1978-1979 (Box-folder 37/12)
  - Me - Kwa - Mooks Park - Newspaper Clippings, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 37/13)
  - Meridian Playground, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 37/14)
  - Meridian Playground, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 37/15)
  - Meridian Playground, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 37/16)
  - Meridian Playground / Good Shepherd, 1977 (Box-folder 37/17)
  - Meridian Playground, 1978 (Box-folder 37/18)
  - Meridian Playground, 1979 (Box-folder 37/19)
  - Meridian Playground, 1980 (Box-folder 37/20)
  - Meridian Playground / Good Shepherd, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 37/21)
  - Meridian Playground Drawings Maps, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 38/1)
  - Meridian Playground - Programs Proposals, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 38/2)
  - Meridian Playground / Good Shepherd Urban Agriculture, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 38/3)
  - Meridian Playground Design Contract, 1977-1981 (Box-folder 38/4)
  - Meridian Playground Dedication, 1981 (Box-folder 38/5)
  - Meridian Playground Bandstand, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 38/6)
  - Meridian Playground Newspaper Clippings, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 38/7)
  - Metro, 1972 (Box-folder 38/8)
  - Miller Playfield, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 38/9)
  - Miller Playfield, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 38/10)
  - Miller Playfield Lighting, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 38/11)
  - Miller Playfield Improvements, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 38/12)
  - Miller Community Center Improvements - Contracts, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 38/13)
  - Miller Community Center Improvements, 1982 (Box-folder 38/14)
  - Miller Community Center Improvements, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 38/15)
  - T.T. Minor Play Area, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 38/16)
  - T.T. Minor Play Area, 1979 (Box-folder 38/17)
  - Mt. Baker Bathhouse Renovation - Contracts, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 38/18)
  - Mt. Baker Bathhouse Renovation, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 38/19)
  - Mt. Baker Play Area Tennis Court, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 38/20)
  - Mt. Baker Rowing and Sailing Facility, 1957-1981 (Box-folder 38/21)
  - Mt. Baker Rowing and Sailing Facility - Survey, 1980 (Box-folder 38/22)
  - Mt. Baker Rowing and Sailing Facility, 1982 (Box-folder 38/23)
  - Mt. Baker Rowing and Sailing Facility, 1983 (Box-folder 38/24)
  - Mt. Baker Rowing and Sailing Facility, 1983 (Box-folder 38/25)
  - Mt. Baker Rowing and Sailing Facility - January, 1984 (Box-folder 38/26)
  - Mt. Baker Rowing and Sailing Facility, 1984 (Box-folder 38/27)
  - Mt. Baker Rowing and Sailing Facility Newspaper Clippings, 1983 (Box-folder 38/28)
  - Mt. Baker Boulevard, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 39/1)
  - Mt. Baker Park - Community Input, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 39/2)
  - Mt. Baker Park, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 39/3)
  - Mt. Baker Youth Services Bureau, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 39/4)
  - Montlake Playfield - Background, 1954-1972 (Box-folder 39/5)
  - Montlake Playfield Acquisition, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 39/6)
  - Montlake Playfield - Legal, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 39/7)
  - Montlake Playfield Contracts Arguments, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 39/8)
  - Montlake Playfield Planning and Program, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 39/9)
  - Montlake Playfield Budget and Financial, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 39/10)
  - Montlake Playfield, 1968 (Box-folder 39/11)
  - Montlake Playfield, 1969 (Box-folder 39/12)
  - Montlake Playfield, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 39/13)
  - Montlake Playfield Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 39/14)
  - Montlake Playfield Correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 39/15)
  - Montlake Playfield, 1973 (Box-folder 39/16)
  - Montlake Playfield - Maps and Drawings, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 39/17)
  - Montlake Playfield, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 39/18)
  - Montlake Recreation Center Contracts and Agreements, 1971 (Box-folder 39/19)
  - Montlake Community Center, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 39/20)
  - Montlake Recreation Center, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 39/21)
  - Montlake Community Center, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 39/22)
  - Montlake Community Center, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 39/23)
  - Montlake Park Tot Lot (includes drawings), 1982-1984 (Box-folder 39/24)
  - Montlake Trail, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 39/25)
  - Museum of History Industry Seattle Art Museum Building Assessment, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 39/26)
  - Museum of History Industry - Painting Windows, 1983 (Box-folder 39/27)
  - Museum of History Industry - Heritage Garden, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 39/28)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park (formerly Elliott Bay) - Background Feasibility, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 39/29)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park (formerly Elliott Bay Park) Property Acquisition, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 39/30)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park (formerly Elliott Bay Park) Reappraisal Lots 2 - 11 Block 167 Seattle Tidelands, 1971 (Box-folder 39/31)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park Land Use / Zoning, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 39/32)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park - Environmental Assessments, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 40/1)
  - Myrtle Edwards - Grant Application, 1974 (Box-folder 40/2)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park Agreements Legislation, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 40/3)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park (formerly Elliott Bay Park) Maps drawings, 1975 (Box-folder 40/4)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park (formerly Elliott Bay Park) Project File, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 40/5)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park (formerly Elliott Bay Park), 1976-1977 (Box-folder 40/6)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park - Budget, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 40/7)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park - Designer Selection Contract, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 40/8)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park (formerly Elliott Bay Park) - Schematics Review, 1974 (Box-folder 40/9)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park - Design Development Review, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 40/10)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park - Construction Site Improvements, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 40/11)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park - Art - Michael Heizer, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 40/12)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park Dedication, 1976 (Box-folder 40/13)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park Construction Phase II, 1978 (Box-folder 40/14)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park Construction Phase II, 1979 (Box-folder 40/15)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park Construction Contracts Change Orders, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 40/16)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park Project File Phase II (includes subsurface drainage drawing other drawings), 1977 (Box-folder 40/17)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park Phase II Project File, 1978 (Box-folder 40/18)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park Phase II Project File, 1979 (Box-folder 40/19)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park Phase II Improvements - Specifications, 1979 (Box-folder 40/20)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park Phase II Project File, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 40/21)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park Phase II Contract - Design Services, 1978 (Box-folder 40/22)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park Phase II Project File, 1981 (Box-folder 40/23)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park Phase II Project File, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 40/24)
  - Myrtle Edwards Park (formerly Elliott Bay Park) Newspaper Clippings, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 40/25)
  - North Administrative Center Park, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 40/26)
  - North Beach Park, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 40/27)
  - North Greenwood / Neil J. Sandel Playground, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 40/28)
  - North Greenwood / Neil J. Sandel Playground Project Description, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 40/29)
  - North Greenwood / Neil J. Sandel Playground Newspaper Clippings, 1969 (Box-folder 40/30)
  - North Greenwood / Neil J. Sandel Playground Contracts and Agreements, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 40/31)
  - North Greenwood Playground / Neil J. Sandel Playground, 1969 (Box-folder 40/32)
  - North Greenwood / Neil J. Sandel Playground - Soils Investigation Report, 1970 (Box-folder 40/33)
  - North Greenwood / Neil J. Sandel Playground, 1970 (Box-folder 40/34)
  - North Greenwood / Neil J. Sandel Playground (includes photographs), 1971 (Box-folder 40/35)
  - North Greenwood / Neil J. Sandel Playground, 1972 (Box-folder 40/36)
  - North Greenwood / Neil J. Sandel Playground, 1973 (Box-folder 40/37)
  - North Greenwood / Neil J. Sandel Playground Acquisition, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 40/38)
  - North Greenwood / Neil J. Sandel Playground, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 40/39)
  - North Leschi Boat Moorage, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 41/1)
  - North Leschi Moorage, 1971 (Box-folder 41/2)
  - North Leschi Moorage, 1972 (Box-folder 41/3)
  - North Leschi Moorage Expansion, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 41/4)
  - North Leschi Moorage, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 41/5)
  - North Leschi Moorage Contracts Agreements, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 41/6)
  - North Leschi Moorage, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 41/7)
  - North Leschi Moorage - Environmental Impact Statement, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 41/8)
  - North Leschi Moorage - Newspaper Clippings, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 41/9)
  - North and South Passage / View Point Parks Contracts Agreements, 1967-1975 (Box-folder 41/10)
  - North and South Passage Point / View Point Park, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 41/11)
  - North and South Passage Point Park, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 41/12)
  - North and South Passage / View Point Parks, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 41/13)
  - North and South Passage / View Point Parks (includes photographs), 1970-1972 (Box-folder 41/14)
  - North and South Passage Point Park, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 41/15)
  - North and South Passage Point Park, 1976 (Box-folder 41/16)
  - North and South Passage Point Parks, 1976 (Box-folder 41/17)
  - North and South Passage Point Parks, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 41/18)
  - Northacres Park - Master Plans, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 41/19)
  - Northacres Park - Community Input (Ten Acre Park), 1959 (Box-folder 41/20)
  - Northacres (Ten Acre) Park - Newspaper Clippings, 1959 (Box-folder 41/21)
  - Northacres Park, 1970 (Box-folder 41/22)
  - Northacres Park, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 41/23)